<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Mind Your Head Co-op]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Mind Your Head Co-op]]></description>
        <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:51:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://mindyourheadcoop.org/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Och! my Head! Understanding TBI Headaches]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Och! my Head! Understanding TBI Headaches</h1><h2>Muscle/Tension Headache:</h2><p>Brain injury bring about some amazing headaches. Some come with light shows and sounds of freight trains. They can leave us debilitated for days in ways we may never have thought possible.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/och-my-head-understanding-tbi-headaches/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0d8d3b6d-b1bf-464a-9519-051ef86d64f6</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relaxing Through The Rocks in the Road]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Relaxing Through The Rocks in the Road</h1><p>“Life is pain, Highness. Anyone who tells you different is selling something.” – Wesley (aka the Great Pirate Roberts) in the film “The Princess Bride”Life with brain injury is often compared to a “long hard road.” It is. It’s got extreme ups and downs plus all kinds of rocks and other challenges. The question is, what do we do about it?</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/relaxing-through-the-rocks-in-the-road/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">50af1efd-86de-40d0-8f2f-03bda31b3f32</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:49:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise Helps Heal the Brain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Exercise Helps Heal the Brain</h1><p>Exercise really does help heal the brain. One of the now known ways it does is by helping generate new mitochondria in the brain and throughout the nervous system. When mitochondria, the powerhouse within each cell of the body, get low neurons risk dysfunction or death. Running the Colorado Trail, along with all other forms of exercise, help heal my brain. What exercise do you find helps heal yours?</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/exercise-helps-heal-the-brain/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a37f341c-2691-4e9a-96a9-1b38502a009e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:47:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Doctors, Doctors everywhere, but Not a One to See!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Doctors, Doctors everywhere, but Not a One to See!</h1><p>Massive change in regulation as a result of Obamacare hit our nation on January first, 2014. Doctors are afraid, and they should be. So should their patients. I understand from a hospital board member that the penalty for a doctor’s first offense of not following the regulation is a $100,000 fine. Second offense is lose of their medical license. If that’s true (and I’ve every reason to believe it is), our government is giving doctors less benefit of the doubt than various criminals, who at least get a three-strike rule in their favor before the heavy consequences hit.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/doctors-doctors-everywhere-and-not-a-one-to-see/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cb16b8ff-ba0b-4d6a-b0ed-a9990283f7af</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:46:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[7. Co-Creation: I’m Ready to Contribute Now…]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>7. Co-Creation: I’m Ready to Contribute Now…</h1><h2>Co-Creating with God</h2><p>Because we are made in God’s image, we have the built in desire to help create God’s vision by doing what we can to make the world a better place.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/co-creation-im-ready-to-contribute-now-stage-7-of-7/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3ec7a5e4-aab8-47e8-977b-d89f71ef778e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:25:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ketogenic Diet Increases Brain Function and Healing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ketogenic Diet Increases Brain Function and Healing</h1><p>Ketogenic simply means getting your primary energy by burning fat, as opposed to most people in the US today who get most of their energy by burning glucose. Science is showing us that when fat is our primary fuel we function much smoother and healthier — including multiple studies showing brain benefits of burning fat os our primary fuel. In essence we access God’s engineering by shifting to burning fat rather than glucose.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/ketogenic-diet-food-for-the-brain/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8639442a-6359-401f-83f4-1f7afd6fc776</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:21:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medical System Acutely Brilliant, Chronically Inept]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Medical System Acutely Brilliant, Chronically Inept</h1><p>If you have an acute medical issue, bones sticking out for example, our medical system is brilliant and providing the care you need. However, if you have a chronic, long term medical issue, such as brain injury, our medical system is no only inept but often harmful and incapable of recognizing either, blaming you instead. Let me explain…</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/null/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9e4a0894-ebb0-4c6b-ad17-a7fe5bf88718</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:19:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Working memory is better after a barefoot run]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Working memory is better after a barefoot run</h1><p>Running barefoot is better than running with shoes for your working memory, according to a new study published by researchers at the University of North Florida.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ce79973c6d2121b487b0934ddd94aabbc571f088.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sciencebulletin.org/archives/906.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0a1240cb-1f0b-4d82-a8cd-66c15466f5ba</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:16:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning and TBI]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Learning and TBI</h1><p>Learning. Och! How personal that process is. How wondrous we all are, each absorbing and processing information so differently. Yet another example of every brain is different, and thus every brain injury is different also. Here’s what I’ve learned about what I need to absorb, think, write, and draw.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/learning-and-tbi/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">476df68a-c46f-485a-ba05-fca22d2b8e6c</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:16:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ode to a Pencil]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ode to a Pencil</h1><p>Ah! What wonder, the pencil! Muttled tangle of jumbled through flows through tis elegant wand and out flows delicate, intricacy and lo! the tangle is tamed! There! Here! Behold!</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mindyourheadcoop.org/ode-to-a-pencil/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f1befaee-a78e-43e4-8e3d-c4f07c58ed86</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:16:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>